Chairperson B-TIT
: O
Outlook B-ORG
Migration B-ORG
Team B-ORG

Detailed O
Description O
: O

Deal O
Terms O

Thanks O
in O
advance O
, O

Audrey B-PER
D I-PER
. I-PER
Robertson I-PER

Transwestern B-ORG
Pipeline I-ORG
Company I-ORG

email B-EML
address I-EML
: I-EML
audrey I-EML
. I-EML
robertson I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
5849 I-TEL

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
2551 I-TEL
Fax O

Thanks O
, O
Gary B-PER

Reyna B-PER
Cabrera I-PER

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
3072 I-TEL

Thanks O
! O

Mike B-PER
McGowan I-PER

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Rick B-PER

John B-PER
Buchanan I-PER

Fran B-PER
Fagan I-PER

Sr B-TIT
. I-TIT
HR I-TIT
Rep I-TIT

Enron B-ORG
Transportation I-ORG
Services I-ORG

713 B-TEL
. I-TEL
853 I-TEL
. I-TEL
5219 I-TEL

fran B-EML
. I-EML
fagan I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Thanks O
, O

Brad B-PER

Miranda B-PER

x3 O
- O
6252 O

Ok O

Yes O
need O
to O
get O
it O
in O
asap O

Larry B-PER

Gary B-PER

thanks O
, O

Joe B-PER
Linhart I-PER

Chris B-PER
Greaney I-PER

Thank O
you O
again O
! O

Chris B-PER
Sebesta I-PER

Northern B-ORG
Natural I-ORG
Gas I-ORG

Office O
: O
402 B-TEL
- I-TEL
398 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7064 I-TEL

Fax O
: O
402 B-TEL
- I-TEL
398 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7413 I-TEL

chris B-EML
. I-EML
sebesta I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Randy B-PER
Bryan I-PER

Market B-TIT
Services I-TIT
Representative I-TIT

Northern B-ORG
Natural I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
Company I-ORG

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
0438 I-TEL

Thanks O
again O
! O

Ken B-PER
Powers I-PER

( B-TEL
402 I-TEL
) I-TEL
398 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7065 I-TEL

MS B-PER

Ava B-PER
- O
35842 B-TEL

Thanks O

Ava B-PER

Maggie B-PER

Toby B-PER
Kuehl I-PER

ETS B-ORG
Electronic I-ORG
Communications I-ORG

Office O
: O
EB O
3946 B-TEL

Phone O
: O
( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
1527 I-TEL

Email O
: O
< O
mailto O
: O
toby B-EML
. I-EML
kuehl I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML
> O
toby B-EML
. I-EML
kuehl I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML
< O
mailto O
: O
toby B-EML
. I-EML
kuehl I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML
> O

Thanks O
: O
John B-PER
Buchanan I-PER

Deborah B-PER

HotTap B-ORG
Helpdesk I-ORG

3 B-TEL
- I-TEL
6063 I-TEL

FYI O

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

- O
- O
- O
- O
- O
Original O
Message O
- O
- O
- O
- O
- O

FYI O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Mike B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER
Blair I-PER

Ricki B-PER
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Large O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

test O

Lynn B-PER

Ava B-PER
, O
please O
put O
me O
on O
the O
list O
. O

Lynn B-PER

This O
is O
fun O
! O
! O
! O
! O

Thanks O
Lynn B-PER

I O
agree O
. O
Thanks O
, O
Lynn B-PER

Fyi O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Fyi O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
, O
Lynn B-PER

Fyi O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Janet B-PER

FYI O
. O
Steve B-PER

Thank O
you O
, O

South B-LOC
Central I-LOC
= I-LOC
20 I-LOC

Randy B-PER

Jamie B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Nancy B-PER

Tracy B-PER
Scott I-PER

ETS B-TIT
HR I-TIT

Anna B-PER
C I-PER
. I-PER
Salazar I-PER

Enron B-ORG
Corp I-ORG

P B-LOC
. I-LOC
O I-LOC
. I-LOC
Box I-LOC
1188 I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
Texas I-LOC
77251 B-TEL
- I-TEL
1188 I-TEL

Tax B-TIT
Accountant I-TIT

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
345 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8722 I-TEL

Nancy B-PER
( B-TEL
x36311 I-TEL
) I-TEL

Amy B-PER

Ricki B-PER

Shane B-PER

Thanks O

Beverly B-PER

Mrs B-PER
. I-PER
Sheila I-PER
Nacey I-PER

8630 B-LOC
Pine I-LOC
Falls I-LOC
Dr I-LOC
. I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
TX I-LOC
77095 I-LOC

Gina B-PER

Tks O
- O
Mike B-PER
W I-PER
. I-PER

Brian B-PER
Robinho I-PER

FT B-ORG
Energy I-ORG

brobinhold B-EML
@ I-EML
ftenergy I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

720 B-TEL
- I-TEL
548 I-TEL
- I-TEL
5722 I-TEL

Terry B-PER
Kowalke I-PER

We O
will O
start O
checking O
these O
for O
May O
Accounting O
, O

The O
TW O
Team O

Mary B-PER

Home O
Address O

10622  B-LOC
Endicott I-LOC
Lane I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
,  I-LOC
TX  I-LOC
77318 I-LOC

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Here O
is O
our O
first O
draft O
. O

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
LYnn B-PER

= O
09FYI O
. O
Thansk O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
, O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O

FYI O
, O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Ava B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Steve B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

= O
09FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
lYnn B-PER

Steve B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thansk O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Sheila B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Did O
you O
receive O
? O

John B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Thank O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Approved O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O

Shelley B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Ava B-PER
, O
no O
problem O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

= O
09Fyi O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

I O
am O
available O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
for O
the O
help O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Lynn B-PER
Blair I-PER

Northern B-ORG
Natural I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
Co I-ORG
. I-ORG

Gas I-ORG
Logistics I-ORG

Phone B-TEL
: I-TEL
( I-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7637 I-TEL
. I-TEL

Fax B-TEL
: I-TEL
( I-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8000 I-TEL

FYI O
. O
thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER 

SLA O
mtg O
, O
. O
Thanks O
Lynn B-PER 

FYI O
. O
Lynn B-PER

= O
09FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

fyi O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Dennis B-PER
P I-PER
. I-PER
Lee I-PER

ETS O

Gas B-ORG
Logistics I-ORG

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
1715 I-TEL

dennis B-EML
. I-EML
lee I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Raetta B-PER

James B-PER

More O
as O
it O
develops O
! O

Your O
pal O
, O

Mike B-PER

Renee B-PER
Perry I-PER
J I-PER

Lori B-PER
Saffer I-PER

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
0641 I-TEL

Sincerely O
, O

Amy B-PER
Mulligan I-PER

Donna B-PER

Thanks O
, O
Kim B-PER
.0

Thanks O
DS B-PER

Pat B-PER
Davidson I-PER

Gas B-TIT
Scheduling I-TIT
Manager I-TIT

Southern B-ORG
California I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
Company I-ORG

pdavidson B-EML
@ I-EML
socalgas I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Thanks O
Ramona B-PER

Elizabeth B-PER

x3  B-TEL
-  I-TEL
6928  I-TEL

- O
Rita B-PER

See O
me O
if O
you O
have O
questions O
. O

Sandra B-PER

thanks O
- O
that O
was O
funny O

have O
a O
great O
day O

sandra B-PER

oh O
- O
laughing O

Who O
is O
Joey B-PER
? O

Warmest O
regards O
, O

Warmest O
Regards O
, O

Sincerely O
, O

thanks O

thnks O

Think O
warm O
thoughts O
Susan B-PER
- O

The B-ORG
Brawner I-ORG
' I-ORG
s I-ORG

15911 B-LOC
Marwick I-LOC
Ct I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
Tx I-LOC
77095 I-LOC

home O
281 B-TEL
- I-TEL
855 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8797 I-TEL

sandra B-PER
cell O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
594 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7369 I-TEL

kenny B-PER
cell O
281 B-TEL
- I-TEL
381 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7288 I-TEL

thanks O
for O
the O
laughs O

i O
love O
you O

Thank O
you O
for O
your O
comments O
. O

Thank O
You O

Best O
Regards O
, O

i O
dont O
book O
these O
trades O

my O
im O
is O
sandra B-PER
brawner I-PER

John B-PER
Craig I-PER
Taylor I-PER

08 O
/ O
16 O
/ O
2000 O
11 O
: O
18 O
AM O

thanks O
- O
did O
it O
last O
week O

Peter B-PER
F I-PER
Keavey I-PER

04 O
/ O
12 O
/ O
2001 O
02 O
: O
24 O
PM O

Love O
and O
Kisses O

Regards O
, O

Jared B-PER

Michael B-PER

Outlook B-ORG
2000 I-ORG
Migration I-ORG
Team I-ORG

I O
love O
you O

Jeff B-PER

Too O
Funny O
! O

See O
below O
from O
Tricia O
Spence O
. O

Good O
Luck O
- O
I O
hoped O
I O
helped O
- O

thank O
you O
for O
the O
invite O
. O
But O
I O
will O
not O
be O
able O
to O
attend O
. O

- O
- O
- O
- O
- O
Original O
Message O
- O
- O
- O
- O
- O

Fangming B-PER

GASFUNDY  B-EML
@ I-EML
ENRON I-EML

11 O
/ O
10 O
/ O
2000 O
10 O
: O
55 O
AM O

Sent O
by O
: O
Chris I-EML
Gaskill I-EML
@ I-EML
ENRON I-EML

To O
: O

cc O
: O
( O
bcc O
: O
Andrea B-PER
Ring I-PER
/ O
HOU O
/ O
ECT O
) O

Thanks O
Again O
for O
the O
time O
, O

Steve B-PER

Aaron B-PER

I O
have O
received O
your O
E O
- O
Mail O
. O

Thanks O
. O

Teresa B-PER

Teresa B-PER
G I-PER
. I-PER
Bushman I-PER

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
TX I-LOC
77002 I-LOC

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7895 I-TEL

Mathew B-PER

Kimat B-PER

Fax O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
345 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7864 I-TEL

HR B-TIT

x35167 B-TEL

Craig B-PER
= O
20 O

Savita B-PER

X31787 B-TEL

fyi O

fyi O
. O
. O
. O

fyi O
. O
. O

Tom B-PER

Kim B-PER

Chris B-PER

3 B-TEL
- B-TEL
7533 B-TEL

November O
8 O
, O
2001 O

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
5193 I-TEL

Leonidas B-PER
G I-PER
. I-PER
Savvas I-PER

Fax O
: O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8453 I-TEL

leonidas B-EML
. I-EML
savvas
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

fyi O
. O

Tammie B-PER
Schoppe I-PER

on O
behalf O
of O
UBS B-ORG
HR I-ORG

Amanda B-PER
Rybarski I-PER

Office O
: O
( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
4384 I-TEL

Fax O
: O
( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
3564 I-TEL

Cell O
: O
( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
560 I-TEL
- I-TEL
0934 I-TEL

Dan B-PER
Diamond I-PER

yep O
, O
that O
my O
son O
! O
! O
! O
! O

Stan B-PER

Enjoy O
! O

The B-ORG
Yahoo I-ORG
! I-ORG
Greetings I-ORG
Team I-ORG

Jon B-PER

Customer B-TIT
and I-TIT
Business I-TIT
Services I-TIT

Global B-ORG
Infrastructure I-ORG

Brian B-PER

David B-PER
Oxley I-PER

http O
: O
/ O
/ O
esource O
. O
enron O
. O
com O

John B-PER

- O
AGA O
' O
00to01Dec8 O
. O
pdf O

- O
Daily O
. O
Dec13 O
. O
pdf O

Many O
Thanks O
, O

Liz B-PER
Taylor I-PER

Assistant B-TIT
to O
Greg B-PER
Whalley I-PER

713 B-TEL
. I-TEL
853 I-TEL
. I-TEL
1935 I-TEL
office O

713 B-TEL
. I-TEL
853 I-TEL
. I-TEL
1838 I-TEL
fax O

713 B-TEL
. I-TEL
854 I-TEL
. I-TEL
3056 I-TEL
mobile O

chance O

Gas B-ORG
Fundamentals I-ORG

Fax O
: O
( B-ORG
713 I-ORG
) I-ORG
646 I-ORG
- I-ORG
8453 I-ORG

Pager O
: O
( B-TEL
877 I-TEL
) I-TEL
482 I-TEL
- I-TEL
0772 I-TEL

Dave B-PER
Forster I-PER

713 B-TEL
. I-TEL
853 I-TEL
. I-TEL
1861 I-TEL

E O
- O
Mail O
: O
David B-EML
. I-EML
Forster I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

David B-PER
Oxley I-PER

Head B-TIT
, I-TIT
Human I-TIT
Resources I-TIT

Thanks O
, O
Tony B-PER
Jarrett I-PER

Benefits O

Ext O
. O
3 B-TEL
- I-TEL
7829 I-TEL

Thank O
you O
, O

Teresa B-PER
Mandola I-PER
( B-TEL
39807 I-TEL
) I-TEL
- O
Power O

Jennifer B-PER
McQuade I-PER
( B-TEL
53614 I-TEL
) I-TEL
- O
Power O

Dan B-PER
Diamond I-PER
( B-TEL
39673 I-TEL
) I-TEL
- O
Gas O

Enron B-ORG
Benefits I-ORG
Department I-ORG

Jeff B-PER
the I-PER
Genius I-PER

Corporate B-ORG
Benefits I-ORG

Lisa B-PER
Shoemake I-PER

East B-ORG
Power I-ORG
Trading I-ORG

EB3125a O

Off O
. O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
9194 I-TEL

Fax O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8272 I-TEL

Stephanie B-PER
Sever I-PER

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
3465 I-TEL

Certification O
Document O

Karen B-PER
Buckley I-PER

Kind O
regards O
, O

Adrianne B-PER

x57302 B-TEL

Louise B-PER

UBSWenergy B-ORG
. O
com O

Stephen B-PER
R I-PER
. I-PER
Harrington I-PER

Technical B-TIT
Project I-TIT
Manager I-TIT
, I-TIT
ECS I-TIT
Project I-TIT

Enron B-ORG
Net I-ORG
Works I-ORG
, I-ORG
LLC I-ORG

w O
: O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7619 I-TEL

p O
: O
877 B-TEL
- I-TEL
651 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7361 I-TEL

c O
: O
713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
444 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7279 I-TEL

stephen B-EML
. I-EML
harrington I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Good O
Luck O

Julie B-PER
: O
- O
) O

Thank O
you O
. O

* O
additional O
offers O

Carolyn B-PER
Graham I-PER

Enron B-ORG
NetWorks I-ORG
LLC I-ORG

Vendor B-TIT
Management I-TIT

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
345 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8008 I-TEL

Stephanie B-PER
Trabia I-PER
ext O
5546 B-TEL

Alan B-PER
Newman I-PER
ext  O
5548 B-TEL

David B-PER
Hewitt I-PER
ext O
5545 B-TEL

Singapore O
( B-TEL
011 I-TEL
) I-TEL
- I-TEL
65 I-TEL
- I-TEL
342 I-TEL
- I-TEL
2931 I-TEL

Soo B-PER
Molyneux I-PER

Charlotte B-PER
Marson I-PER

http O
: O
/ O
/ O
pacmembers O
. O
enron O
. O
com O

I O
have O
a O
seperate O
system O
. O
1 O

I O
believe O
1 O
. O

Sincere O
Regards O
, O

Enjoy O

Sandra B-PER
Brawner I-PER

thnks O

i O
dont O
get O
it O

Rick B-PER

fyi O
, O
rick O

please O
schedule O

test3 O

Attached O

thanks O
, O
rick B-PER
buy B-PER

Weird O
, O
but O
ok O
by O
me O
. O
Rick B-PER
Buy I-PER

test2 O

feb O
2 O
i O
think O
why O
? O
? O

Rick B-PER
Buy I-PER

keep O
' O
em O
coming O
, O
rick B-PER

Best O
of O
luck O
, O
Rick B-PER

excellent
!
!
!
!
!

I
have
done
this
3
times
now
.

Is
this
correct
?
Rick

Thanks
,
Rick

Call
me
if
a
problem
,
Rick
Buy

How
is
progress
on
this
?
Rick

fyi
,
please
respond
,
tx
rick

fyi
-
comments
?
rick

will
not
attend
,
tx
rick

fine

to
your
hearts
content

Thanks
,
Rick
Buy

What
conference
?
Rick

fine
by
me
,
rick

This
is
fine
by
me
.
Rick
Buy

Please
print
and
file
tx
rick

Lisa
Fair

(
+
44
207
783
7123
)

Thanks
.
.
dy

Any
news
on
this
.
Rick

Has
this
been
verified
.
Rick

Molly

Regards

Bill

01
/
02
/
2000
00
:
34

Any
progress
here
.
Rick

Any
more
on
this
issue
.
Rick

Did
this
go
ok
.
Rick

Kathy
Mayfield

12
/
13
/
2000
05
:
02
PM

12
/
13
/
2000
05
:
07
PM

Thank
you
in
advance
.

Dorothy

Vickie

EB4836

713
-
853
-
9864

Per
your
request
.

Tanya

Jim

3

Please
see
attached
.

Aren
'
t
we
all
?

Charla
Reese

Manager
,
Community
Relations

x35202

Pam

Kent
W
.
Morrison

KM
Business
Analyst
Consultant

Thanks
.

LI52100

HAPPY
HOLIDAYS

Lee
Steele

Manager
Enron
Networks

(
713
)
345
-
8259

Emy
C
.
Geraldo

3
-
5391

Enron
Corp
.

Enron
Europe
Gas
Trading
VaR
Violation

From
:
Rick
Causey

Dial
in
-
011
44
207
783
0508

Dial
In
for
Domestic
:
1
-
877
-
987
-
1409

Leaders
Name
:
Gary
Hickerson

Pass
Code
:
Gary

Lisa
Fair

+
44
207
783
7123

To
be
rescheduled
.

Domestic
800
-
745
-
1000

International
801
-
977
-
0648

Code
8531935

Attorney
:
J
.
C
.
Nickens

s
&
p

Pager
:
713
-
764
-
6467

Frank

ASME
International

Capitol
Update

October
24
,
2001

Public
Affairs
Program
Manager

1828
L
Street
,
NW
,
Suite
906

Washington
,
DC
20036

Phone
:
202
.
785
.
3756

Fax
:
202
.
429
.
9417

Email
:
legatskim
@
asme
.
org

regards
,

RZ

The
New
York
Times
on
the
Web

Ned
Crady

Enron
Global
Markets

Office
:
(
713
)
853
-
4552

Email
:
ncrady
@
enron
.
com

Caroline
Bond

Managing
Director

Melissa
R
.
Murray

Government
Relations

Phone
:
202
.
785
.
7380

Email
:
murraym
@
asme
.
org

William
W
.
Brown

Cheers
big
ears
,

Jules

Cassandra
.

Sharon
Sullo

x31946

Thanks
,
Julie

To
future
success
,

Chris
Risenhoover

Regional
Account
Manager

Tripwire
,
Inc
.

972
-
306
-
1658
(
voice
)

801
-
327
-
6548
(
fax
)

ChrisR
@
Tripwire
.
com

www
.
Tripwire
.
com

"
Boldness
has
genius
,
power
,
and
magic
in
it
.
"

-
Goethe

James
Buzek

Enron
Net
Works

713
-
345
-
3510

Talk
to
you
soon
,

Julie

Thanks
again
,

Kevin

Hema
Malini

Hema
@
Izhuta
.
com

Phone
:
1
800
485
7004
ext
202

http
:
/
/
www
.
Izhuta
.
com

Rita

Wendy
Conwell

Dave

Sue

Kelly
M
.
Johnson

Tel
:
713
-
853
-
6485

Fax
:
713
-
853
-
2534

E
-
Mail
:
kelly
.
johnson
@
enron
.
com

David
L
.
Belden

Executive
Director

Mary
James
Legatski

Government
Relations
Representative

Best
regards
,

Sato

Enron
Japan

Julie
Haviland

Senior
Registered
Account
Adminstrator

Emery
Financial
Group
of

Regards
,
akp

Regards
,

Frank

Donna
Wackerle

Sr
.
Admin
Asst
.

Compliance

713
-
853
-
9755

503
-
464
-
2663

Lee
,

Look
forward
to
receiving
your
email
.

Thanks
again
.

Bridge
Line
Information

Monica

Ed
Sacks

Rick
,

I
received
this
from
Dawn
Derr
in
Corporate
Accounting
.

Cheers
,

Amy
Schram

Marketing
Manager

Subsurface
Consultants
&
Associates

2500
Tanglewilde
,
Suite
120

Houston
,
Tx
77063

713
.
789
.
2444

713
.
789
.
4449
fax

Cindy

Harris
713
-
368
-
2309

Montgomery
936
-
539
-
7843

Waller
979
-
826
-
7643

Brazoria
979
-
864
-
1320

Fort
Bend
281
-
341
-
8670

Liberty
936
-
336
-
4629

Chambers
409
-
267
-
8301

Galveston
409
-
766
-
2280

Monica
Reasoner

Karen
Thiessen

Program
Manager
&
Senior
Research
Associate

Business
Research
Group

The
Conference
Board
of
Canada

1
-
613
-
526
-
3090
,
ext
.
245

thiessen
@
conferenceboard
.
ca

Tori
L
.
Wells

Office
of
Ken
Lay

Chairman
&
CEO

ENRON

Joannie

3
-
1769

DP

FINAL

Doug

Douglas
A
.
Leyendecker

Leyendecker
&
Associates

713
-
862
-
3030

http
:
/
/
www
.
leyendecker
.
com

Ted

PRELIMINARY

Are
you
aware
of
this
?

Wanda

Mark

Time
:
6
:
00pm

Place
:
Kenneally
'
s

Carol
North

Don
Rollins

Enron
Corporation

Risk
Assessment
&
Control

713
-
853
-
9176

Sally
=
20

Rocky
V
.
Emery

Emery
Financial
Group

of
First
Union
Securities
,
Inc
.

713
-
853
-
2400

Vince

Vince
Kaminski

I
will
keep
you
advised
.

Robert

Marcus

Greg
Piper

Sally
Beck

Mark
Pickering

PARTICIPANTS
:
Lisa
Mellencamp

1
-
3769

Jeffrey
McMahon
and
Ray
Bowen

Thanks
.
Paula

Please
advise
,

Clare
Fitzgerald

marcus
evans

303
E
.
Wacker
Drive
,
20th
Floor

Chicago
,
IL
60601

Ph
:
312
-
540
-
3000x6785

Fx
:
312
-
894
-
6390

Ben

Gordon

Tracey
Kozadinos

Risk
Assessment
&
Control
-
Reporting

713
.
853
.
3446

Maribel
M
Monterrey

Donna
Lowry

Cheers
loser
,

Gina
Corteselli

Dennis

Molly

Alice
Wright

Assistant
to
Elizabeth
Sager

1400
Smith
St
.
,
EB3809A

Houston
,
Texas
77002

Tel
:
713
-
853
-
5438

Fax
:
713
-
646
-
3491

alice
.
wright
@
enron
.
com

See
attached
:

No
failures
today
.

Maribel
M
Monterrey

Office
:
(
713
)
853
-
9048

Fax
:
(
713
)
853
-
9476

Maribel
.
Monterrey
@
enron
.
com

Rich
Christiansen

fyi
,
draft
8
-
k
below
:

Attendees
:
Rick
Buy

http
:
/
/
erv
.
corp
.
enron
.
com

Terri
Bachand

Enron
Global
Finance

(
713
)
853
-
6528

Thank
you
kindness
and
I
look
forward
to
hearing
from
you
.

Stephanie

3
-
9283

Please
call
if
you
have
any
questions
.

No
Failures

Rosie

Valeria
Hope
-
HR
Rep
(
3
-
7573
)

Human
Resources

Becky
Zikes

(
713
)
853
-
1843

<
<
memo
to
Buy
.
doc
>
>

Risk
Waters
Group

28
-
29
Haymarket

London
,
UK

SW1Y
4RX

Tel
:
00
44
(
0
)
20
7484
9700

Mailto
:
listadmin
@
riskwaters
.
com

EDD

0766576

Jim
Derrick

Cristal
Metz

Executive
Assistant
,
PGE

503
-
464
-
8997

cristal_metz
@
pgn
.
com

Louise
Kitchen

Chief
Operating
Officer

Enron
Americas

Tel
:
713
853
3488

Fax
:
713
646
2308

Harry
Saul

HAPPY
NEW
YEAR
,

Cheryl
Hasan

Coordinator
,
Member
Recruitment

Thanks
and
regards
,

joan

Many
thanks
!
!

SAP
Security
(
Eva
)

Thanks
-

John
Suttle

Thanks
for
your
continued
understanding
.

Rgds

Manager
,
State
Government
Relations

3
-
3831

Executive
Assistant
to
Jim
Fallon

Office
of
the
Chairman

Enron
Broadband
Services

Fax
713
-
345
-
7864

Cell
713
-
417
-
7802

lucy
.
marshall
@
enron
.
com

Handouts
only
.

Best
regards
,

Chip

Happy
New
Year
by
the
way
.

Dal
Coger

Principal

Britt
Davis

Enron
Litigation
Unit

3
-
6307

Parking
&
Transportation
Desk

3
-
7060

Shona
Wilson

Director
,
Global
Risk
Operations

X39123

Tsunami
Partners

Executive
Search
&
Selection

Ph
#
781
-
395
-
2981

Ph
#
781
-
874
-
0527

Cell
781
-
718
-
8397

Fax
781
-
395
-
2719

wireless
email
7817188397
@
msg
.
myvzw
.
com

web
site
http
:
/
/
tsunamipartners
.
tripod
.
com

Stig
Faltinsen
(
UK
)

Kirstee
Hewitt
(
UK
)

781
-
395
-
2981

Kimm
Cashiola

Mariner
Energy
,
Inc
.

Executive
Assistant

to
VP
Finance
&
Administration

End
User
Support
Help
Desk

(
281
)
584
-
5571

(
281
)
584
-
5690
Fax

Bj
?
rn
Hagelmann

Director

Rac
-
Market
Risk
Management

E
-
Mail
:
bjorn
.
hagelmann
@
enron
.
com

Office
:
+
1
713
345
7984

Trade
Floor
:
+
1
713
345
0338

Mobil
:
+
1
281
451
4156

?
Corp
$
68
.
9MM
$
60
.
7MM

?
Americas
$
46
.
5MM
$
39
.
6MM

?
Gas
$
17
.
6MM
$
23
.
8MM

?
Power
$
48
.
9MM
$
49
.
5MM

?
So
.
Cone
Pwr
$
239K
$
239K

?
So
.
Cone
Gas
$
63K
$
63K

Liz
Fricke

Many
thanks
,

Lucy

Madeline

Thank
You
,

Yes
,
it
is
.

Andrew

Got
it
.
It
'
s
fine
.

Here
'
s
the
e
-
mail
again
.

Kevin
Garland

The
Sterling
Group

Eight
Greenway
Plaza

Houston
,
Texas
77046

Work
Phone
:
713
-
877
-
8257

Cell
Phone
:
713
-
598
-
1653

kgarland
@
sterlinggrp
.
net

Sheila
Walton

Stacey
-
power
is
ok
too

Tks

looked
harmless
-
I
sent
it

Tammie
Schoppe

Enron
Americas
-
Office
of
the
Chair

Assistant
to
Louise
Kitchen

713
.
853
.
4220
office

713
.
646
.
8562
fax

713
.
253
.
2131
mobile

http
:
/
/
www
.
kenron
.
net
/

Best
regards

Pam
Butler

Date
:
December
11
,
2001

Time
:
9
:
00
AM
CST

Location
:
ECN
5C2
(
old
building
)

Laura
Valencia

Tel
:
713
-
853
-
6485

Fax
:
713
/
853
-
2534

Marcy
Brinegar

MBM
Consultants

(
770
)
886
-
6202
(
Office
)

(
678
)
234
-
7644
(
Cell
)

(
770
)
886
-
8202
(
fax
)

brinconsult
@
aol
.
com

mbmconsult
@
adelphia
.
net

Sharon

David

Paul
D
.
Flack

Clements
,
O
'
Neill
,
Pierce
,
Nickens
&
Wilson
,
L
.
L
.
P
.

1000
Louisiana
,
Suite
1800

Houston
,
Texas
77002

(
713
)
654
-
7615

(
713
)
654
-
7690
(
fax
)

flack
@
copn
.
com

Additional
requests
from
UBS
.

Assets
Dave
Gorte
/
Michael
Tribolet

London
Ted
Murphy

EES
Jay
Hachen

Knock
yourself
out
.

web
site
<
http
:
/
/
tsunamipartners
.
tripod
.
com
/
>

LaMetrice
Dopson

Global
Infrastructure
-
Senior
Director

Enron
NetWorks

(
770
)
886
-
6202

web
site
"
http
:
/
/
tsunamipartners
.
tripod
.
com
/
"

Shona

Thanks
for
your
help
.

Amy

cell
:
713
-
859
-
6266

send
non
-
enron
-
email
.

Delainey

Owner
:
Karen
K
Heathman

Report
Name
:
Brad
Larson

Days
In
Mgr
.
Queue
:
7

Love
,

Kind
regards
,

Urs
Widmer

UBS
Warburg

Sharon

Karen

Sr
.
Director

RAC
Compliance

(
713
)
853
-
1939

(
713
)
646
-
4039
fax

dp

Doug

Paula

Rob
Walls
John
Ale

x6
-
6017
x5
-
5263

Cell
(
713
)
562
-
7572
Cell
(
713
)
305
-
8263

cc
:
Jim
Derrick
,
Lance
Schuler

Greg

Thanks
so
much
for
your
help
!

Kortney
Brown

x30616

Imelda
:

Bel
Gas
Phy
Option
product
customer
profile
list
approved
from
credit
.

Gabriel

Thanks
-
Janet
&
Dan

Michelle
Wenz

713
-
853
-
0920

michelle
.
wenz
@
enron
.
com

Sheila

Tina
Spiller

Assistant
to
Greg
Piper

President
&
CEO

Enron
Net
Works
LLC

Phone
713
.
853
.
5746

Fax
713
.
646
.
8070

Rick
Carson

Hard
Copy
:

Wanda
Curry

Lori
Pinder

Supervisor
,
Corporate
Services

and
Assistant
Secretary

1400
Smith
St
.
,
Room
4922

713
.
853
.
6099

Melissa
Magley

Days
In
Mgr
.
Queue
:
6

Ray

Ted
and
acquantances

Chrissy
Grove

Network
Security

713
.
345
.
8269

Andrew
Gibbins

Enron
Contract
Management

Enron
House
,
40
Grosvenor
Place

London
SW1X
7EN

Tel
:
+
44
(
0
)
20
7783
4711

Fax
:
+
44
(
0
)
20
7783
9240

Scott
Marra

Administrator
for
Policy
and
Media
Relations

600
Fifth
Avenue

Rockefeller
Center
-
27th
floor

New
York
,
NY
10020

Phone
:
(
212
)
332
-
2578

Fax
:
(
212
)
332
-
1212

Email
:
smarra
@
isda
.
org

Kelly
Boots

Thanks
-
Dan

kcashiola
@
mariner
-
energy
.
com
<
mailto
:
kcashiola
@
mariner
-
energy
.
com
>

Marion
Sczykutowicz

marion
.
sczykutowicz
@
enron
.
com

713
/
853
-
5331

713
/
646
-
8517
(
Fax
)

Ankush

Steven

cell
713
305
4883

Kelly

Cindy
Hudler

Risk
Assessment
&
Control
-
Underwriting

1400
Smith
St
.

Houston
,
Tx
77002
-
7361

P
:
713
.
853
.
6944

F
:
713
.
646
.
3601

E
:
cindy
.
hudler
@
enron
.
com

Cassandra
=
20

Stay
Safe

Bill
Reid

CEO
-
netR
&
M

(
972
)
814
-
4678

www
.
netr
-
m
.
com

Terri

x33565

Not
sure
what
to
make
of
it
.
Any
input
would
be
appreciated

Hang
in
there
.

Done
.

karl

Samantha
Davidson

357
N
Post
Oak
Ln
#
113

Houston
,
TX
77024

(
713
)
853
-
4294
Work

(
713
)
680
-
8898
Home

(
713
)
907
-
4678
Mobile

texastaryn
@
netscape
.
net

Here
it
is

Lea
Savala

Herbert
S
.
Winokur
,
Jr
.

Capricorn
Management
,
G
.
P
.

203
-
861
-
6600

203
-
861
-
6671
(
fax
)

Sincerely
yours
,

Yoram
Dankner

Naveen
Andrews
(
58668
)
.

jeff

Ravi
Thuraisingham
,
CFA

Director
,
Storage
Trading
,

EBS
Global
Wholesale
Markets

713
-
853
-
3057
desk

713
-
516
-
5440
cell

Peter
Antoniadis

416
-
217
-
4166

1400
Smith
Street
EB
3882A

Houston
,
Texas
77002

Phone
:
(
713
)
853
-
1575

Fax
:
(
713
)
646
-
3393
/
3490

Joni
Fisher

Billy

Distribution
:

Executive
Committee

Recruiting
Executive
Leads

Cassandra

(
and
Scott
Vonderheide
)

(
no
change
from
yesterday
)

GP

Rebecca
Skupin

Enron
Media
Services

713
-
853
-
3314

Rob

Rob
Brown

Manager
,
Enron
Corp
.

Financial
Accounting
&
Reporting

Off
.
713
.
853
.
9702

Cell
713
.
303
.
4497

rob
.
brown
@
enron
.
com

Days
In
Mgr
.
Queue
:
5

Vlady
.

Chip
Schneider

713
-
853
-
1789

3AC
1418

No
Failures
today
.

Sherron
S
.
Watkins

Vice
President
,
Enron
Corp
.

713
-
345
-
8799
office

713
-
416
-
0620
cell

VaR

Jeffrey
McMahon

Tracy

503
-
464
-
8755

Bill
Dorsey
.

Wendy

x30699

Susan

Administrative
Coordinator

Enron
Wholesale
Services

Legal
Department

Telephone
:
(
713
)
853
-
7906

Fax
:
(
713
)
646
-
2600

e
-
mail
:
janette
.
elbertson
@
enron
.
com

KG

1400
Smith
Street
EB
824

Fax
:
(
713
)
646
-
8860

Chris
Abel

Manager

Global
Risk
Controls

Donna
M
.
Cagle

Executive
Administrator
to
President
&
CEO

580
WestLake
Park
Blvd
.
,
Suite
1300

Houston
,
TX
77079

281
/
584
-
5511
(
phone
)
281
/
584
-
5515
(
fax
)

dcagle
@
mariner
-
energy
.
com

Thanks
,
Mariella

Daily
Loss

Aparna
Rajaram

Ph
:
(
713
)
345
-
4563

Aparna
.
Rajaram
@
enron
.
com

With
Best
Regards
,

Rohel
Mahmud

Account
Manager

Zaconta

Tel
#
248
351
0015
ext
.
313

Fax
#
248
351
5627

email
:
rohelm
@
zaconta
.
com

website
:
www
.
zaconta
.
com

Alix
Gage

Email
:

Days
In
Mgr
.
Queue
:
4

Any
thoughts
?

Jo

Jim
Lobdell

Vice
President

Risk
Management
,
Reporting
,
Controls
&
Credit

Portland
General
Electric

(
503
)
464
-
2723

Rodney

Cindy
Stark

Executive
Assistant
to
Stan
Horton

Tel
:
713
/
853
-
6197

Fax
:
713
/
345
-
7047

Cindy
.
Stark
@
enron
.
com

Rgds
,

(
713
)
345
-
7712

Geoff
Kates

Thank
You
,

Hank
Emery

An
SPE
Gulf
Coast
Section

Business
&
Technology
Workshop

Final
Violation
Memos

RSVP
to
joy
.
wagman
@
enron
.
com

Limited
spaces
are
available
.

Thomas
Severance

Director
North
American
Sales

<
http
:
/
/
www
.
algorithmics
.
com
/
>

The
Woodlands
Resort
&
Conference
Center

2301
N
.
Millbend
Drive

The
Woodlands
,
TX
77380

Phone
:
281
-
367
-
1100

Fax
:
281
-
364
-
6299

3
-
1879

Atos
Origin

Kind
regards
.

Prameesh
Barlota

Tel
:
513
-
985
1421
Fax
:
513
-
793
5062
Mobile
:
513
-
314
7075

Ken

MRP

Rick
C
.

Max
Sonnonstine

x5
-
8261

Kortney

Dale
Schuett

Senior
Account
Executive

WhiteLight
Systems

(
925
)
462
-
2497
Office

dale
@
whitelight
.
com
<
<
Bank
Technology
News_Dresdner
.
htm
>
>

www
.
whitelight
,
com

Thanks
,

Thanks
for
your
help
!

Agenda
:

8
:
30
-
8
:
50
:
Daily
officialization
status

8
:
50
-
9
:
30
:

Please
call
w
/
any
questions
.

Let
'
s
discuss
in
the
coming
weeks
.

Like
it

Shirley
Cox

Assistant
to
Sheila
Walton

51721

