Chairperson B-TIT
: O
Outlook B-ORG
Migration B-ORG
Team B-ORG

Detailed O
Description O
: O

Deal O
Terms O

Thanks O
in O
advance O
, O

Audrey B-PER
D I-PER
. I-PER
Robertson I-PER

Transwestern B-ORG
Pipeline I-ORG
Company I-ORG

email B-EML
address I-EML
: I-EML
audrey I-EML
. I-EML
robertson I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
5849 I-TEL

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
2551 I-TEL
Fax I-TEL

Thanks O
, O
Gary B-PER

Reyna B-PER
Cabrera I-PER

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
3072 I-TEL

Thanks O
! O

Mike B-PER
McGowan I-PER

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Rick B-PER

John B-PER
Buchanan I-PER

Fran B-PER
Fagan I-PER

Sr B-TIT
. I-TIT
HR I-TIT
Rep I-TIT

Enron B-ORG
Transportation I-ORG
Services I-ORG

713 B-TEL
. I-TEL
853 I-TEL
. I-TEL
5219 I-TEL

fran B-EML
. I-EML
fagan I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Thanks O
, O

Brad B-PER

Miranda B-PER

x3 O
- O
6252 O

Ok O

Yes O
need O
to O
get O
it O
in O
asap O

Larry B-PER

Gary B-PER

thanks O
, O

Joe B-PER
Linhart I-PER

Chris B-PER
Greaney I-PER

Thank O
you O
again O
! O

Chris B-PER
Sebesta I-PER

Northern B-ORG
Natural I-ORG
Gas I-ORG

Office B-TEL
: I-TEL
402 I-TEL
- I-TEL
398 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7064 I-TEL

Fax B-TEL
: I-TEL
402 I-TEL
- I-TEL
398 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7413 I-TEL

chris B-EML
. I-EML
sebesta I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Randy B-PER
Bryan I-PER

Market B-TIT
Services I-TIT
Representative I-TIT

Northern B-ORG
Natural I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
Company I-ORG

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
0438 I-TEL

Thanks O
again O
! O

Ken B-PER
Powers I-PER

( B-TEL
402 I-TEL
) I-TEL
398 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7065 I-TEL

MS B-PER

Ava B-PER
- O
35842 B-TEL

Thanks O

Ava B-PER

Maggie B-PER

Toby B-PER
Kuehl I-PER

ETS B-ORG
Electronic I-ORG
Communications I-ORG

Office B-TEL
: I-TEL
EB I-TEL
3946 I-TEL

Phone B-TEL
: I-TEL
( I-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
1527 I-TEL

Email O
: O
< O
mailto O
: O
toby B-EML
. I-EML
kuehl I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML
> O
toby B-EML
. I-EML
kuehl I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML
< O
mailto O
: O
toby B-EML
. I-EML
kuehl I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML
> O

Thanks O
: O
John B-PER
Buchanan I-PER

Deborah B-PER

HotTap B-ORG
Helpdesk I-ORG

3 B-TEL
- I-TEL
6063 I-TEL

FYI O

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

- O
- O
- O
- O
- O
Original O
Message O
- O
- O
- O
- O
- O

FYI O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Mike B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER
Blair I-PER

Ricki B-PER
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Large O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

test O

Lynn B-PER

Ava B-PER
, O
please O
put O
me O
on O
the O
list O
. O

Lynn B-PER

This O
is O
fun O
! O
! O
! O
! O

Thanks O
Lynn B-PER

I O
agree O
. O
Thanks O
, O
Lynn B-PER

Fyi O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Fyi O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
, O
Lynn B-PER

Fyi O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Janet B-PER

FYI O
. O
Steve B-PER

Thank O
you O
, O

South B-LOC
Central I-LOC
= I-LOC
20 I-LOC

Randy B-PER

Jamie B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Nancy B-PER

Tracy B-PER
Scott I-PER

ETS B-TIT
HR I-TIT

Anna B-PER
C I-PER
. I-PER
Salazar I-PER

Enron B-ORG
Corp I-ORG

P B-LOC
. I-LOC
O I-LOC
. I-LOC
Box I-LOC
1188 I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
Texas I-LOC
77251 B-TEL
- I-TEL
1188 I-TEL

Tax B-TIT
Accountant I-TIT

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
345 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8722 I-TEL

Nancy B-PER
( B-TEL
x36311 I-TEL
) I-TEL

Amy B-PER

Ricki B-PER

Shane B-PER

Thanks O

Beverly B-PER

Mrs B-PER
. I-PER
Sheila I-PER
Nacey I-PER

8630 B-LOC
Pine I-LOC
Falls I-LOC
Dr I-LOC
. I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
TX I-LOC
77095 I-LOC

Gina B-PER

Tks O
- O
Mike B-PER
W I-PER
. I-PER

Brian B-PER
Robinho I-PER

FT B-ORG
Energy I-ORG

brobinhold B-EML
@ I-EML
ftenergy I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

720 B-TEL
- I-TEL
548 I-TEL
- I-TEL
5722 I-TEL

Terry B-PER
Kowalke I-PER

We O
will O
start O
checking O
these O
for O
May O
Accounting O
, O

The O
TW O
Team O

Mary B-PER

Home O
Address O

10622  B-LOC
Endicott I-LOC
Lane I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
,  I-LOC
TX  I-LOC
77318 I-LOC

Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Here O
is O
our O
first O
draft O
. O

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
LYnn B-PER

= O
09FYI O
. O
Thansk O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
, O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O
~ O
* O

FYI O
, O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Ava B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Steve B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

= O
09FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
lYnn B-PER

Steve B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thansk O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Sheila B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Did O
you O
receive O
? O

John B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Thank O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Approved O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O

Shelley B-PER
, O
FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Ava B-PER
, O
no O
problem O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

= O
09Fyi O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

I O
am O
available O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Thanks O
for O
the O
help O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Lynn B-PER
Blair I-PER

Northern B-ORG
Natural I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
Co I-ORG
. I-ORG

Gas I-ORG
Logistics I-ORG

Phone B-TEL
: I-TEL
( I-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7637 I-TEL
. I-TEL

Fax B-TEL
: I-TEL
( I-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8000 I-TEL

FYI O
. O
thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

SLA O
mtg O
, O
. O
Thanks O
Lynn B-PER

FYI O
. O
Lynn B-PER

= O
09FYI O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

fyi O
. O
Thanks O
. O
Lynn B-PER

Dennis B-PER
P I-PER
. I-PER
Lee I-PER

ETS O

Gas B-ORG
Logistics I-ORG

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
1715 I-TEL

dennis B-EML
. I-EML
lee I-EML
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Raetta B-PER

James B-PER

More O
as O
it O
develops O
! O

Your O
pal O
, O

Mike B-PER

Renee B-PER
Perry I-PER
J I-PER

Lori B-PER
Saffer I-PER

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
0641 I-TEL

Sincerely O
, O

Amy B-PER
Mulligan I-PER

Donna B-PER

Thanks O
, O
Kim B-PER
.0

Thanks O
DS B-PER

Pat B-PER
Davidson I-PER

Gas B-TIT
Scheduling I-TIT
Manager I-TIT

Southern B-ORG
California I-ORG
Gas I-ORG
Company I-ORG

pdavidson B-EML
@ I-EML
socalgas I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML

Thanks O
Ramona B-PER

Elizabeth B-PER

x3  B-TEL
-  I-TEL
6928  I-TEL

- O
Rita B-PER

See O
me O
if O
you O
have O
questions O
. O

Sandra B-PER

thanks O
- O
that O
was O
funny O

have O
a O
great O
day O

sandra B-PER

oh O
- O
laughing O

Who O
is O
Joey B-PER
? O

Warmest O
regards O
, O

Warmest O
Regards O
, O

Sincerely O
, O

thanks O

thnks O

Think O
warm O
thoughts O
Susan B-PER
- O

The B-ORG
Brawner I-ORG
' I-ORG
s I-ORG

15911 B-LOC
Marwick I-LOC
Ct I-LOC

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
Tx I-LOC
77095 I-LOC

home B-TEL
281 I-TEL
- I-TEL
855 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8797 I-TEL

sandra B-PER
cell B-TEL
713 I-TEL
- I-TEL
594 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7369 I-TEL

kenny B-PER
cell  B-TEL
281 I-TEL
- I-TEL
381 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7288 I-TEL

thanks O
for O
the O
laughs O

i O
love O
you O

Thank O
you O
for O
your O
comments O
. O

Thank O
You O

Best O
Regards O
, O

i O
dont O
book O
these O
trades O

my O
im O
is O
sandra B-PER
brawner I-PER

John B-PER
Craig I-PER
Taylor I-PER

08 O
/ O
16 O
/ O
2000 O
11 O
: O
18 O
AM O

thanks O
- O
did O
it O
last O
week O

Peter B-PER
F I-PER
Keavey I-PER

04 O
/ O
12 O
/ O
2001 O
02 O
: O
24 O
PM O

Love O
and O
Kisses O

Regards O
, O

Jared B-PER

Michael B-PER

Outlook B-ORG
2000 I-ORG
Migration I-ORG
Team I-ORG

I O
love O
you O

Jeff B-PER

Too O
Funny O
! O

See O
below O
from O
Tricia O
Spence O
. O

Good O
Luck O
- O
I O
hoped O
I O
helped O
- O

thank O
you O
for O
the O
invite O
. O
But O
I O
will O
not O
be O
able O
to O
attend O
. O

- O
- O
- O
- O
- O
Original O
Message O
- O
- O
- O
- O
- O

Fangming B-PER

GASFUNDY  B-EML
@ I-EML
ENRON I-EML

11 O
/ O
10 O
/ O
2000 O
10 O
: O
55 O
AM O

Sent O
by O
: O
Chris I-EML
Gaskill I-EML
@ I-EML
ENRON I-EML

To O
: O

cc O
: O
( O
bcc O
: O
Andrea B-PER
Ring I-PER
/ O
HOU O
/ O
ECT O
) O

Thanks O
Again O
for O
the O
time O
, O

Steve B-PER

Aaron B-PER

I O
have O
received O
your O
E O
- O
Mail O
. O

Thanks O
. O

Teresa B-PER

Teresa B-PER
G I-PER
. I-PER
Bushman I-PER

Houston B-LOC
, I-LOC
TX I-LOC
77002 I-LOC

( B-TEL
713 I-TEL
) I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7895 I-TEL

Mathew B-PER

Kimat B-PER

Fax B-TEL
713 I-TEL
- I-TEL
345 I-TEL
- I-TEL
7864 I-TEL

HR B-TIT

x35167 I-TEL

Craig B-PER
= O
20 O

Savita B-PER

X31787 B-TEL

fyi O

fyi O
. O
. O
. O

fyi O
. O
. O

Tom B-PER

Kim B-PER

Chris B-PER

3 B-TEL
- B-TEL
7533 B-TEL

November O
8 O
, O
2001 O

713 B-TEL
- I-TEL
853 I-TEL
- I-TEL
5193 I-TEL

Leonidas B-PER
G I-PER
. I-PER
Savvas I-PER

Fax B-TEL
: I-TEL
713 I-TEL
- I-TEL
646 I-TEL
- I-TEL
8453 I-TEL

leonidas B-EML
. I-EML
savvas
@ I-EML
enron I-EML
. I-EML
com I-EML